神烦警探  第三季第二十二集
翻译  A.I.
翻译  waterdancing
翻译  RT1
校对  好吧蛋蛋
后期  柒一四
深影字幕组出品
犹太人在星期日的问候语
脱口秀Live with Kelly的前主持人Regis Philbin雷吉斯・菲尔宾
迈克・斯特拉恩2012年起开始担任该节目主持人
欲望都市的主人公
225641441636324行动
FBI大楼
前美联储主席
半开襟上衣 类似无领polo衫
吉娜 很抱歉我错怪你了
我召集你们过来
I called you here
是要讨论225641441636324行动的进展
to discuss where we are with Operation 225641441636324.
啥
What?
我把"皮门托"的每个字母以数字表示
I assigned a numerical value to each letter
再将其平方
in the word "Pimento," which I then squared.
警监
Oh, Captain.
你居然敢把数学掺和进来
How dare you try and sneak math into this?
佩拉尔塔
Peralta.
汇报一下桑提亚戈监狱卧底行动的最新情况
Update us on Santiago's undercover prison operation.
是 她已经跟吉米・菲吉斯的妹妹有了接触
Yeah, she has made contact with Jimmy Figgis' sister,
但进展缓慢
but it's slowgoing.
我希望她能快点回来
I hope she comes back soon.
你想她了
You miss her?
不 我本来要帮她喂鱼
No, I lost the key to her apartment,
但我把她公寓的钥匙弄丢了
and I'm taking care of her fish.
它们已经都死了 是吧
They're all dead already, aren't they?
- 是 - 该死
- Yeah. - Damn it.
我们的首要目标仍然是找出菲吉斯在FBI的内线
Our priority is still finding Figgis' agent in the FBI.
我觉得是时候请我在局里工作的
I think it's time for me to call in a favor
老同事 鲍勃・安德森 帮个忙了
from an old colleague at the bureau, Bob Anderson.
我早就该联系他 但这毕竟是私自行动
I would've contacted him sooner, but this is a rogue op,
而他是个循规蹈矩的人
and he's a real stickler for the rules.
有一次他在街上捡到了一分钱
He once picked up a penny off the street, which he then
然后在报税时算进去了
reported on his taxes.
听起来是个有趣的人啊
Sounds like a barrel of laughs.
很幸运 他并不是
Fortunately, he isn't.
我们以前共事过 配合得很好
We worked together back in the day and really hit it off.
咱们要在这呆上一阵了
We're going to be here a while.
想聊天吗
Would you like to talk?
还是别聊了
I'd rather not.
同意
Agreed.
天啊
Oh, man.
跟联邦调查局的人秘密会面
A secret FBI meet up?
简直一级棒
I love this!
看看那些白痴
Look at all those idiots.
完全不知道将要发生什么
They have no idea what's about to go down.
你是说那个女人和她的小宝宝吗
You mean that woman and her baby?
对 白痴
Yep. Idiots.
鲍勃来了
Oh, here comes Bob.
别淘气
Please behave.
你好 鲍勃
Hello, Bob.
很高兴见到你
Good to see you.
幸会 抱歉
And you. Apologies.
在尊驾手下警探面前
It's inappropriate for me to partake in such
进行此等非正式交谈并不合适
informal conversation in front of your detectives.
不必过谦 在下亦当自责
It's all right. I am equally to blame.
天啊
Oh, my God.
他俩一样一样的
There's two of them.
那么 雷蒙德 你有什么证据证明
So, Raymond, what evidence do you have
联邦调查局内部有被买通的探员
that there's a dirty agent in the FBI?
拿卷宗来看看吧
Let's see the file.
我们没有卷宗
We don't have a file.
你在无卷宗情况下工作
You're working file-less?
我们看到那人犯罪了
We saw the guy commit a felony.
他试图杀死一名警察
He tried to have a cop killed.
性感到爆的警察
Crazy hot cop.
他属于很小众的类型
Well, he's a specific type.
我们要找的人当时带着滑雪面罩
Look, the guy we're looking for was wearing a ski mask,
身高约一米七八 白人
but he's about 5'10". Caucasian.
他右手上有个很大的疤
He's got a big scar on his right hand.
我们一直管他叫刀疤乔 就像女演员
We've been calling him ScarJo, like the actress,
斯嘉丽・约翰逊的简称
Scarlett Johansson.
什么 女演员
What? An actress?
我真不知道出处是这里
I didn't know that was where that was from.
鲍勃 我很抱歉
Bob, I'm so sorry.
- 没事 我就当没听见 - 好的
- No, I'll look past it. - Okay.
有个探员符合你们的描述
There's an agent that matches that description.
他名叫瑞安・ 惠伦
His name is Ryan Whealon.
如果你看到他 能认出来吗
You think you could ID him if you saw him?
能 我在二十英里开外都能认出来
Oh, yeah. I'd recognize that scar from 20 miles away.
你的视力一定特别好
You must have fantastic vision.
也可能是那条疤极其大
Or it's a gigantic scar.
我明显是在夸张
I was clearly exaggerating.
你们就不能配合一下吗
Why do you have to ruin everything?
施瓦茨医生 我按时来就诊了
Dr. Schwartz, I'm here for my appointment.
你好 科尔特斯 安息日平安
Hello, Cortez. Shabbat Shalom.
"安息日平安"
"Shabbat Shalom"?
没办法 杰克让我扮成犹太人
I don't know. Jake made me Jewish.
莫拉那边进展如何
So how are things going with Maura?
我现在是她手下了
Well, I'm part of her crew,
但她仍不肯提起她的过去
but she still won't talk about her past.
你以前在纽约都干些什么啊
So, what kind of stuff did you used to do in New York?
你问这么多问题干嘛 雷吉斯
What's with all the questions, Regis?
其实现在是迈克・斯特拉恩主持了
Actually, it's Michael Strahan now.
啥
What?
她太吓人了
She's so scary.
我亲眼看到她把自己的牙拔下来扔到另一个女人的眼睛上
I saw her pull her own tooth out and throw it into a woman's eye.
太恐怖了 你猜怎么着
Yeah, that's bad. So guess what.
吉纳维芙刚来短信
Genevieve just texted.
我们的领养申请随时会有结果了
We're gonna hear about our adoption any minute.
你们不是去进行治疗了吗
I thought you were doing fertility treatments.
是去了 但不太顺利
We are, but it's not going well.
医生说我的不孕症太猛烈
The doctor said my sterility is so aggressive,
- 可能已经把她传染了 - 好吧
- it may have spread to her. - Okay.
但是 领养也很好啊 查尔斯
But, adoption! Charles, that's amazing!
- 是啊 - 坏了
- I know! - Oh, no.
- 什么 - 莫拉
- What? - Maura.
总的说来 科尔特斯小姐 你的阴道看起来很棒
Anyway, Ms. Cortez, your vagina looks great.
恭喜
Mazel.
你看今天早晨的报纸了吗
Did you see this morning's newspaper?
没有 我都是通过
No. I get all my news
我朋友们的群发消息了解新闻的
from a text message chain with my friends.
司法部长可能要辞职了
The attorney general might step down!
逗你呢 是一张小兔子吃意面的动图
I'm kidding. It's a GIF of a rabbit eating spaghetti.
有一篇关于九九区月度犯罪率的文章
There's an article about the Nine-Nine's monthly crime rate.
那些数据本该是下周才公布的
Those numbers aren't supposed to be public until next week.
泰瑞 如果你想听到 "我去" 这两个字
Terry, you're gonna have to be more interesting
你得说点更有趣的
if you want to get an "Oh, dang."
九九区有人泄密了
There's a leak in the Nine-Nine!
我去
Oh, dang.
我在一次晨会中公布过那些数据
I presented those numbers in a morning briefing,
但我想不出谁会笨到把它们泄露出去
but I can't imagine anyone would be stupid enough to leak 'em.
真的吗 泰瑞斯 看看他们有多笨
Really, Terrence? Look how dumb they are.
打印机修好了
Printer's fixed.
我去
Oh, dang.
跟佩拉尔塔说 惠伦正在接近
Tell Peralta Whealon's approaching.
那个混蛋来了
Here comes the douche bag.
灰西装 自然点
Gray suit. Act natural.
看看 多好的杂志啊
Wow, look at that. What a great magazine.
先生 你要是喜欢
Sir, if you're interested,
新一期的《小丑咪咪》刚到货
the new issue of "Clown Boobies" just came in.
我可以开箱给你拿一本
I can unpack the box for you.
什么
What?
不用了 我就要上一期的
Actually, no. I need last month's.
我就想看这一期的某个
There's a particular clown...
小丑的... 咪咪
booby... that I'm looking for.
佩拉尔塔干嘛呢
What is Peralta doing?
他看起来像是在浏览
He appears to be rifling through
"小丑咪咪杂志"
"Clown Boobies Magazine."
笨手笨脚的
Stupid butterfingers.
- 没关系 - 谢谢
- It's all right. - Thank you.
给你
Here you go.
谢谢 非常感谢
Thank you. Thank you so, so much.
不谢谢 一点都不谢谢 你个垃圾
Not thank you. Not thank you at all, you dirtbag.
科尔特斯
Hey, Cortez!
你跟那个医生怎么回事
What's going on with you and that doctor?
关系貌似很好啊
You seem real tight with him.
不 没什么好的 一点都不熟
No, we're not tight. I barely know him.
那你干嘛要抱他
So why were you hugging him?
我的上诉被拒了 他在安慰我
My last appeal got denied, so he was comforting me.
他是个感性的人 可能因为他信犹太教吧
He's a sensitive guy. Maybe because of his Jewish faith.
我要跟他谈谈 单独谈
I want to talk to him. Alone.
是看病吗 还是...
Oh. About something medical? Or...
我是怎么跟你说问题太多的人来着
What did I tell you about asking too many questions?
对了 那是你杀了一群婊子的原因
Right. That's that thing you killed a bunch of bitches for.
知道了 对不起
Ah. Got it. Sorry.
我们已经监视他一整天了
We've been watching this guy all day.
真不敢相信居然还没逮捕他
Can't believe we haven't even arrested him yet.
明明已经确定是他了
We know he's the guy.
我们得先掌握证据
We have to build a case first.
下午四点十三分 目标喝完了咖啡 或者是茶
4:13 p.M. Subject finishes his coffee. Or tea.
把饮料标记为"未知"
Mark the beverage as "Unknown."
警探们好
Detectives.
联邦调查局的数据库
What does the FBI database
有什么关于惠伦和菲吉斯的信息
tell us about Whealon and Figgis?
他们俩的档案全都被删除了
Both of their files were completely wiped.
我从没见过这种情况
I've never seen that before.
那是因为他有罪
Yeah, that's because he's guilty,
而我们只是坐在这看他吃桃子
and we're just sitting here watching him eat a peach.
那是个油桃
That's a nectarine.
不是油桃就是桃子
It's either a nectarine or a peach.
就写"未知有核水果"吧
Just write "Unknown stone fruit."
不可能只有电子档案的
There can't just be digital files.
肯定会有纸质档案
There must be hard copies.
那些都锁在档案室里
Those are all under lock and key in the archives.
如果我申请查阅 可能会打草惊蛇
If I asked for clearance, they could alert him.
有趣
Interesting.
照你这么说 我们只好
So what you're saying is our only option
闯入联邦调查局偷走档案
is to break into the FBI and steal the file.
别扯淡了
Don't be absurd.
鲍勃 我为他扯的淡向你道歉
Bob, I apologize for the absurdity.
我觉得不是扯淡
I see no absurdity.
实际上 我认为佩拉尔塔说得对
Actually, I think Peralta's right.
咱们来策划一起劫案吧
Let's plan a heist.
鲍勃
Bob?
联邦调查局纽约总部的设计图
Blueprints for the New York Headquarters of the FBI.
我们要找的资料
The file we're looking for
在档案室 这里 地下室
is in the archive room, here, in the basement.
就用我兜里的东西代表我们几个吧
We will be represented by these things I had in my pocket.
只有绒球 我兜里只有绒球
All I had was lint. Just a pocketful of lint.
大家都记住自己的绒球长啥样
Everybody remember what your lint looks like.
我的绒球是圆的
My lint is round.
我的绒球直径约一厘米
My lint is approximately 1 centimeter in diameter.
- 我的绒球是蓝色的 - 我的绒球是椭圆的
- My lint is blue. - My lint is oblong.
我的绒球长约半厘米
My lint is approximately 1/2 centimeter in length.
我的绒球也是蓝色的
My lint is also blue.
都不反对用线头吗 那太好了
Wow, so no pushback on the lint thing? This is great.
我可以让你们顺利进入前门
Now, I can give you clearance to get in the front door,
但要进档案室又是另一回事了
but getting into the archive is another matter.
如果能进到这个卫生间 我就能顺着这个通风口
If I go into this bathroom, I could climb through this vent,
顺着爬到档案室 然后盗取文件
drop down into the archive room, and steal the file.
你怎么出来呢
How are you gonna get out?
爬上去原路返回
Pull myself back up the way I came in.
干嘛 我可以做引体向上 泰瑞会教我的
What? I can do a pull-up. Terry will teach me.
这整片区域都由这里的保卫
This whole area is video-monitored
视频监控
by this guard here.
我可以借聊天分散他的注意力
I can distract him with conversation.
你了解他什么情况吗
What do you know about him?
他看很多电视剧
Watches a lot of TV.
我听他提过《欲望都市》
I heard him mention "Sex and the City."
那我就跟他聊聊这两部剧
Then I will discuss both of those shows with him.
《欲望都市》是一部电视剧
Ooh. "Sex and the City" is one show.
不是一部叫《欲望》
It's not a show called "Sex"
另一部叫《都市》
and then another show called "The City."
好吧 开了个好头
Okay. Good start.
现在我就懂了
Now I know that.
我可以关掉监控录像
I can disable the security DVRs,
但我需要设法悄悄靠近操作台
but I need some way of getting to a station unnoticed.
我有个主意能把你偷偷送进去
I have an idea on how to smuggle you in,
不过会有点挤
but it'll be a tight fit.
我柔韧性很好 我练了很久瑜伽
I'm flexible. I do a lot of yoga.
你练瑜伽
You do yoga?
有助我集中注意力 要是你再问一次
Helps keep me centered. If you ask me about it again,
我会追杀你然后把你脸皮撕掉
I'll hunt you down and rip your face off.
行 很好 好计划 我不会再问了
Okay. Great. Good plan. I won't ask you about it again.
我负责搞定监控
I got the DVRs.
实际上 那是我的绒球 我的绒球是椭圆形的
Actually, that's my lint. My lint is oblong.
我的绒球是蓝色的
My lint is blue.
好了 看来我们已经做好了计划 那就开始训练吧
Okay! Sounds like we've got a plan. Let's get to training.
她为什么要见我
Why does she want to meet with me?
你觉得我们暴露了吗
You think our cover's blown?
我不知道 不过为了安全起见
I don't know, but, just to be safe,
我们来复习下你的背景故事
let's review your backstory.
我上的是叶史瓦医学院 在西奈山医院做住院医
I went to Yeshiva med school, residency at Mount Sinai,
我最好的朋友是杰科比・佩尔贝格
my best friend is Yacob Peralberg,
我们对彼此畅无不言
and we share everything with each other.
没想到会有最后这部分 不过还行
Can't imagine that last part coming up, but okay.
你行的
You got this.
伊莎贝尔
Well, Isabel,
你的胎儿头部大小正好
your baby's head is the perfect size.
谢谢 大夫
Oh, thank you, doctor.
不过生产的时候还是会痛的 做好准备吧
Still gonna hurt when it comes out. Get ready for that.
你就是施瓦茨医生
So you're Dr. Schwartz.
是我 你好啊 我能为你效劳吗
That's me. L'chaim. How can I help you?
从你一露面我就在观察你
I've been watching you ever since you showed up here.
你似乎跟以前那些医生都不一样
You don't seem like the other doctors that we've had.
有趣... 我最好的朋友杰科比也常这么说
It's funny... my best friend, Yacob, is always saying that.
废话少说
Cut the crap.
- 你我都清楚我来这的原因 - 是吗
- We both know why I'm here. - We do?
你的心跳已超速
Your heart's beating a mile a minute.
并不是因为我紧张了
It's not because I'm nervous!
科尔特斯说你很感性 我喜欢
Cortez says that you're sensitive. I like that.
我只跟骗人的渣男在过一起
I've only been with cheating scum.
直到现在
Until now.
出什么事了吗
Everything okay in here?
- 没事 - 一切正常
- Yeah. - We're all good.
他刚在给我检查身体
He was just checking me out.
我会很快再来的 医生
And I will see you soon, doctor?
回见
Later.
Yeah. Later.
都怪这个完美的屁股
Curse this perfect butt.
你怎么能这么说 长官
How dare you, sir?
你真的以为我们会故意泄露消息吗
Do you really think we would leak information on purpose?
不 我们认为你们两个笨蛋无意中说漏了
No. We think you're dum-dums and you did it by accident.
好吧 那倒是很有可能
Oh. Well, that's very possible.
是 我觉得也是
Yeah, I could see that.
那次晨会是一周前开的
The briefing was a week ago.
告诉我们你们之后接触过的所有人
Just tell us everyone you talked to since then.
我想想 星期六 我跟朋友们聚会
Well, let's see. On Saturday, I got together with my friends,
我们去看了赛狗
and we went to the dog track.
名字写下来
We need names.
我撒谎了 其实没几个朋友
I lied. There's not multiple friends.
只有斯库利
It's just Scully.
好吧 那你呢 斯库利
Okay. What about you, Scully?
我跟一个兄弟去看了纽约尼克斯队的比赛
Well, I went to the Knicks game with a buddy.
这个兄弟是不是叫希区柯克
Was this "Buddy" named Hitchcock?
是的 而且我们没看球赛
Yes, and we weren't at the game.
我们是去看了赛狗
We were at the dog track.
拜托 伙计们
Oh, come on, guys.
你们还可能跟什么人聊过犯罪数据
Is there anyone you could've told the crime stats to?
- 犯罪数据 - 等等 你俩有谁
- Crime stats? - Wait. Do either of you
知道我们的逮捕人数吗
even know what our arrest numbers were?
- 十二个 - 不对
- 12. - No!
- 那就不知道 - 不是他们泄露的
- Then no. - Yeah, they're not the leak.
加油 伙计 运用你的肌肉
Come on, man. Use your muscles.
运用我的肌肉 太好了
Use my muscles? Oh, great.
为什么我就没想到呢
Why didn't I think about that?
好建议 泰瑞
Great advice, Terry.
这只不过是引体向上而已
You know what? It's a pull-up.
根本没什么好教的
There's not much to coach here.
人物有凯莉 米兰达 夏洛特和萨曼莎
So there's Carrie, Miranda, Charlotte, and Samantha,
不过纽约其实是第五个人物
but New York City is really the fifth character.
史蒂夫呢 他似乎是个好人
Hmm. What about Steve? He seems nice.
史蒂夫什么也不是 没人喜欢史蒂夫
Oh, Steve is nothing. No one likes Steve.
"史蒂夫什么也不是"
"Steve is nothing."
好吧
Okay!
我不懂了 米兰达本来可以跟布莱尔・安德伍德在一起的
I don't get it. Miranda could've had Blair Underwood,
但她却跟了史蒂夫
but she settled for Steve?
你其实搞懂了 长官 看 你现在就懂了
Oh, but you do get it, sir. See, now you do.
你那么做对我有什么帮助
How is you doing that helping me?
- 斯库利 - 罗莎
- Scully. - Rosa.
很棒 你能安静地做一个吗
Good job. Can you do it without screaming?
也... 许... 吧
Pro-bab-ly.
那我们准备好了
Then we're ready.
我们去闯联邦调查局吧
Let's break into the FBI.
不是吧 警监 这么重要的时刻
Oh, come on, Captain. This is such a big moment.
语气再热烈一点
Say it with more gusto.
的确 应该这样
Indeed. Like this:
我们去闯联邦调查局
let's break into the FBI.
我懂了
Oh, I see.
我们去闯联邦调查局
Let's break into the FBI.
不对 我们去闯联邦调查局
No. Let's break into the FBI.
我们去闯联邦调查局
Let's break into the FBI.
我们去闯联邦调查局 我觉得不错了
Let's break into the FBI. I feel like I'm doing it.
我们去闯联邦调查局
Let's break into the FBI.
好了 我觉得可以了
Okay! I think we got it.
现在
Now,
我们去闯联邦调查局啦
let's break into the FBI!
早上好
Good morning.
- 你好 这是你的 - 谢谢
- Hi. This is for you. - Thanks.
你这分量可不轻啊
Quite a big package you've got there.
抱歉 我用了双关语
Oh, I apologize for the double entendre.
我真像萨曼莎
I can be such a Samantha.
真的吗
Really?
你看起来可不像萨曼莎
You don't seem like a Samantha.
其实我是
Well, I'm actually a combination
四人的合体
of all four characters.
如果把纽约市算在内的话就是五人
Five if you count the city of New York.
没错
Yes.
你也是《欲望都市》脑残粉吗
Another Sex-and-the-Citiot?
我认罪
Guilty as charged.
我最喜欢的是第三季
My favorite season has to be the third one.
凯莉当时顺风顺水
Everything was going right for Carrie.
她的照片上了公交车 专栏也成了热门话题
Her face was on every bus, her column was the talk of the town,
她还认识了大家最爱的家具制造商
and she met everyone's favorite furniture maker,
艾登・肖
Aidan Shaw.
当然 他想带她见父母时
Sure, she melted down when he tried to introduce her
她崩溃了 然后当她撞见
to his parents, and she flipped out
新婚的大人物和娜塔莎从出租车里出来时
when she bumped into Big getting out of that cab
她都快气疯了
with Natasha, whom he had married.
也不能怪她
Hmm. Who can blame her?
他们几乎不了解对方
They barely knew each other.
那一季最好看的一集...
The best episode that year...
是第六集 标题是《我们是荡妇吗》
was episode six, entitled "Are We Sluts?"
就那集 凯莉满脑子都在想
You know the one. Carrie was all in her head
她和艾登没发生关系
because she and Aidan weren't having sex.
与此同时 在城市另一边
Meanwhile, across town,
夏洛特沉溺在性爱中无法自拔
Charlotte couldn't stop having sex.
还有萨曼莎 萨曼莎还是老样子
And Samantha? Samantha was just being Samantha.
那一季的最后一集题目是《喔喔喔》
The season finale that year was entitled "Cock-a-Doodle-Do."
喔喔喔 收到
Cock-a-doodle-doo. Roger that.
哎呀
Whoops.
我讨厌大人物
I hate Big!
凯莉本来应该跟米哈伊・巴瑞辛尼科夫在一起的
Carrie should've ended up with Mikhail Baryshnikov.
什么 他扇了她耳光 你傻吗
What? He slapped her! Are you insane?
搞定
Bingo.
拿到文件了 准备撤离
Got the file. Preparing for extraction.
不许出声 佩拉尔塔
No screaming, Peralta.
要我说的话 他们根本就不该拍电影
If you ask me, they never should've made the movie.
什么阿布达比 可别费事了
Abu Dhabi? Abu don't bother.
这个笑话我用得着
Wow. I'm gonna use that.
- 请尽管用 祝你愉快 - 好的
- Please do. Have a nice day. - Okay.
给你
Hey. Here you go.
等一下 站住 你们两个
Whoa, wait. Hold on. Stop. Both of you.
那个通行证只能进九楼
That pass is only for the ninth floor.
好了 我要检查那个信封
All right. Let me see that envelope.
实际上 我不能给你看 因为...
Oh, actually, I can't show you that, because...
没事
It's okay.
是我叫他下来寄东西的
I asked him to come down and mail that.
我只要把回邮地址写上去
I just need to put my return address on it.
来 给你
And... there you go.
谢谢 我知道应该放到哪里
Thanks. I know just where to put that.
我又萨曼莎上身了
Oh! There's Samantha again.
我们成功了
Whoo-hoo-hoo! We did it!
怎么 我只是个凡人
What? I'm only human.
你不能总是指望
You can't always expect me
我做史上最冷静之人
to be the coolest guy ever.
史上最冷静之人 跟艾伦・格林斯潘说去吧
Coolest guy ever? Try telling that to Alan Greenspan.
吐槽得好 鲍勃
Nice burn, Bob!
我应该料到莫拉
I should've known Maura
控制不了自己
wouldn't be able to control herself.
强势的女人总是会被我吸引
Strong women, they're just drawn to me.
她们都像直角那么直
You know, they're all right angles,
而我却像曲线那样平滑
and I'm nothing but curves.
这其实是件好事 伯耶尔
This actually could be great, Boyle.
你可以借机引诱她开口 不过
You could romance her into talking, but you shouldn't
如果你反感的话 那就算了
do anything that you're not comfortable with.
不 我不反感 又不会有身体接触
Oh, no. No, I won't have to. It's not gonna get physical.
诱惑的艺术就在于让上钩的人一直候着
You see, the art of seduction is all about making people wait.
- 对 - 我和吉纳维芙
- Right. - Genevieve and I
在做爱之前通常...
often begin our lovemaking sessions...
行了
Oh. Okay.
都会聊好几个小时
With hours upon hours of delicateness...
- 好了 别说了 - 这样会激起...
- Okay. Please stop. - That kind of blow...
警卫
Guard!
- 你明白吧 - 明白了
- You get it. - All right. Yeah.
好的  勾人欲望的歌单 有了
All right. Sexy playlist. Check.
诱人的声音 也有
Seductive voice. Double check.
嘿 花栗鼠
Hey, chipmunk.
- 我们来吧 - 好啊
- Let's do this. - That sounds fun.
但先让我签一些表格
But first, I need to sign some charts,
因为我是名非常 好的 医生
because I am a really... good... doctor.
赶紧把你的翘臀送过来
好 我会的
Oh, I will!
谁是吉纳维芙
Who is Genevieve?
没谁
No one!
是我的脊椎按摩师
My chiropractor.
- 那接电话吧 - 接电话
- Then answer it. - Answer it?
可是我们何不享受此时此刻
I mean, why don't we just stay in the moment?
为什么要拘泥于这些小盒子
Why are you such a slave to these little boxes?
接电话 开扩音
Answer the phone, and put it on speaker.
你好
Hello?
亲爱的 领养申请已经批准了
Honey, the adoption papers went through!
你要成为父亲了
You're gonna be a daddy!
我的天 我要有孩子了
Oh, my God! I'm having a baby!
你打错了 别再打过来了
I mean... this is the wrong number. Don't call here again!
你死定了
You're dead.
是你死定了 求你别打我
Maybe you're dead. Please don't hurt me.
在干嘛 警长
Sup, Sarge?
像正常人一样挖垃圾吗
Just digging through the garbage like a normal person?
我在查谁是泄密者
I'm trying to find out who our leak is.
你怎么就这么确定有人泄密
What makes you so sure that there's a leak?
也许只是那个记者很称职呢
It might've just been that the reporter was really good
就像TMZ八卦网那个性感的金发冲浪者一样
at his job, like that hot blond surfer was at TMZ?
可能是你泄露的
Maybe you leaked it.
什么
Excuse me?
我不是说你有意泄露
I'm not saying you did it on purpose.
你可能把文件落在地铁上了
Maybe you left the file on the subway.
你工作态度不是很严谨
I mean, you don't take your job very seriously.
哇 现在我们要
Whoa. We're about to have
像两口子一样吵架了吗 泰瑞斯
our first fight as a couple, Terrence.
首先 我有很认真工作
First of all, I take my job very seriously.
因此我才会在这里帮你
That's why I'm here right now, helping you,
而且只有我一个人帮你
and I'm the only one doing it.
直到你侮辱我之前都是
Or, I was, until you insulted me.
现在看我离去的背影吧
Now watch me walk away.
我说了看着我
I said watch me!
难怪惠伦清除了数据
Wow. No wonder Whealon wiped the database.
看这里
Look at this.
他终止了FBI和纽约警局
He quashed all FBI and NYPD operations
与菲吉斯有关的所有行动
relating to Figgis...
贩毒 绑架 谋杀
drug running, kidnapping, murder...
多重要的案子啊 为什么你们要终止调查
those are the best crimes; why would you quash them?
等待的时间已经结束
Time for waiting is over.
现在是时候直击对方要害了
Now is the time for groin-stomping.
对 正是如此
Damn right, it is!
我们去抓那个臭小子
Let's go arrest that punk.
他说"臭小子"的口气好像你
He says "Punk" Just like you.
你以为他是跟谁学的 臭小子
Where do you think he learned it, punk?
纽约警察
NYPD!
- 有人来过这里 - 尸体
- Somebody's been here. - A body!
- 发现尸体 - 该死的
- We got a body! - Damn it!
他死了 菲吉斯先找到他了
He's dead. Figgis got to him.
等等 他还有脉搏
Wait a minute. He's got a pulse.
不 等等 是我的脉搏
No, wait. That's my pulse.
不 是他的脉搏 不对 是我俩的
No. It's his pulse. Nope, it's both our pulses.
他还没死 我也没死 我们都没死
He's alive! I'm alive! We're all alive!
这案子要真相大白了
This case just got busted wide open.
好消息
Good news.
医生说惠伦不会死
The doctors say Whealon's not gonna die.
谢天谢地 但愿他受尽痛苦折磨
Thank God. I just hope he's in a lot of pain.
他们说惠伦会在十二小时内醒过来
They say he'll be out of the coma within 12 hours.
太好了 他绝对会指证菲吉斯
Great. That means he'll definitely testify
而这也就意味着
against Figgis, and you know what that means:
是时候来条巧克力棒庆祝一下
time for celebration candy bars!
医院那些辣鸡自动贩卖机
Stupid hospital vending machines
不知为啥都不卖酒 来一条
didn't have alcohol for some weird reason. Here.
有何不可 我今天真想放纵一回
Why not? I really have embraced my wild side today.
我也是
As have I.
坚果巧克力
Chocolate and nuts.
还是有点过分了
Actually, that's overkill.
太过分了
Indeed.
我在这里等
I'll wait here,
这样他一醒我就能问他话
so I can interrogate him when he wakes up.
我和你一起
I'll keep you company.
你们两个回家洗洗睡吧
Why don't you two go home and get some sleep?
好 长官
Good idea, sir.
我们先去酒吧喝得烂醉
We'll head to the bar, get super drunk,
然后回家倒头大睡
and then head home and get some sleep.
对 好主意 长官
Yeah. Good idea, sir.
事实证明 你那个感性的医生并不是那么回事
Turns out your sensitive doctor isn't who he says he is.
什么 你什么意思 怎么说
What? What do you mean? Why?
因为他和他的脊椎按摩师要一起领养孩子
'Cause he's about to adopt a baby with his chiropractor.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God...
你不用再为这段感情 这个混蛋
that you didn't invest more time in a relationship
投入更多时间
with that jerk.
我怎么就找不到好男人呢
Why can't I find a good man?
也许是因为你因谋杀而入狱
Could be because you're in prison for murder.
- 不可能 才不是 - 对 绝对不是
- Nah. That's not it. - Yeah, that's not it.
进来之前 我和我哥帮派里的朋友
Before this, I used to date all my brother's friends
全都约过
from the mob.
狗也是
All dogs too.
算了 你不想听这些的
Never mind. You don't want to hear about them.
不 我想听
No! I do want to hear about them.
来吧 全都说给我听
Please. Tell me everything about them.
谢了 你真好
Thanks. That would be nice.
啊 你不喜欢别人碰你 明白
Ahh! Not a toucher. Totally get it.
我会管好自己的手
I'll keep my hands to myself.
怎么样了 警长 找到泄密的人了吗
What's going on, Sarge? You find that leak yet?
是啊 我躲在咖啡机后 监视办公室里的每一个人
Yes. I'm hiding behind a coffeemaker, spying on everyone
因为我已经找到泄密的人了
in this office, because I found the leak.
哎呀 泰瑞 冷嘲热讽的形象真的不适合你
Aww, Terry. Sarcasm is not a good look on you.
但你知道什么适合你吗
But you know what would be?
- 紧身的亨利衫 - 真是谢谢你了
- A really tight Henley. - Very helpful.
我知道是谁泄密了
I know who your leak is.
啥
What?
我查了那个报道犯罪数据的记者
I looked up the reporter who published the crime numbers,
我发现你们俩互相关注了
and I noticed you two follow each other online.
是他先关注我的 你也知道
He followed me, and you know I'm
我这人最喜欢回粉
a proud member of team follow-back.
所以我查了你的主页
So I went through your feed
看看你都发了什么
to see what you were posting.
很多你孩子的照片 并没有人在意
Lots of pictures of your kids. Nobody cares.
然后我发现了上周你发的这张图
And then I found this picture you posted last week.
"享受#优格 生活"
"Living that #YOGURT life."
真是无语
Embarrassing.
不过泰瑞 更让人无语的是
But what's even more embarrassing, Terry,
逮捕人数就在照片上 写得清清楚楚
is that the arrest numbers are in the photo, clear as day.
我的天
Oh, my God!
是我泄露的
I was the leak!
我得删掉那张照片
I got to take that picture down.
吉娜 很抱歉我错怪你了
Gina, I am so sorry I blamed you.
我早就知道你会这么说
And I knew you would say something like that,
所以我提前替你给自己
so I went ahead and bought myself a cake
买了个蛋糕
on your behalf.
瞧
Check it out.
我去
Oh, dang.
这蛋糕都放在这里半小时了 警探大人
And this has been here for the last half-hour, detective.
居然都没察觉
Didn't even notice it.
天哪 老是要帮别人做事 真受不了
God, I'm so sick of doing everyone's job for them.
谁来帮我一点忙啊
It's like, help me out a little bit.
百年都难得一次
Just once in a blue moon.
我们做到了
Well, we did it.
有那么一瞬间 我还以为
For a second there, I didn't think
我们完不成任务了
we were going to pull it off.
- 我知道我们可以 - 我们也是 干杯
- I knew we could. - And we did. To us!
你们俩在庆祝什么
Oh. What are you guys celebrating?
泰瑞对我们乱发脾气 但我们
Terry was mad at us, but we didn't know
不知道他在说什么 然后他就走了
what he was talking about, and he went away.
真是个大日子
Huge day.
是艾米
It's Amy.
嘿 亲爱的
Hey, girlfriend.
杰克 莫拉跟我说了
Jake, Maura told me
FBI里为菲吉斯办事的那个人
who Figgis has working for him in the FBI.
我已经知道是谁了
Yeah, I already know who it is,
因为我刚刚抓到他了
because I just caught him:
是特工瑞安・ 惠伦
Special Agent Ryan Whealon.
我还做了个引体向上呢
Also, I did one full pull-up.
等你回来我就成猛男了
I'm gonna be so buff when you get back.
酷 宝贝 你们抓到另一个人了吗
Cool, babe. Did you get the other guy?
- 什么另一个人 - 名叫鲍勃・安德森的家伙
- What other guy? - Someone named Bob Anderson.
鲍勃
Bob?
我的天
Oh, my God.
艾米 我得挂了
Amy, I have to go.
- 鲍勃在给菲吉斯办事 - 什么
- Bob is working for Figgis. - What?
肯定就是他删掉了电子档案
He must've been the one who deleted all those digital files.
他还想杀掉惠伦
And he tried to have Whealon killed.
可他帮我们盗取了文件
But he helped us with the heist,
而且他的档案也没什么异样
and there was nothing about him in the paper file.
因为那份不是真的档案
Yeah, because that wasn't the real file.
我只要把回邮地址写上去
I just need to put my return address on it.
来 给你
And... there you go.
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
我们得联系霍尔特
We have to call Holt.
快 警监 快接啊
Come on, Captain. Pick up. Pick up.
别接电话 雷蒙德
Don't answer that, Raymond.
我现在不得不杀了你
And now I'm going to have to kill you.
噢 鲍勃
Oh, Bob.